viberate.com 2018-06-27

# Privacy policy | Viberate – biggest live music community

### PRIVACY POLICY

We’ve updated our Privacy Policy to reflect the requirements set by General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). Changes to the Privacy Policy include:

  * your right to request the list of your personal information that we keep;
  * your right to manage or delete any or all personal information;
  * your right to deactivate your account and be forgotten;
  * your right to opt-out of receiving promotional content at any time.

To continue using your account and Viberate’s services, you’ll have to read and agree with our updated Terms of Service and Privacy Policy when logging into your account or registering on our website.

#### Intro

This Privacy Policy sets out how Viberate uses and protects any information that you give us when using Viberate.com. We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. All information provided by you will only be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Privacy Policy may be changed, revised or amended by Viberate by posting the changes under this section. You are advised to periodically visit the Privacy Policy page to review the current Privacy Policy.

#### Collected Information

Viberate may collect the following information: - Basic information such as your first and last name. - Contact information including email address and phone number. - Demographic information such as postal code, age, and gender. - Other relevant information (profession, music taste, preferences and interests). - Your logo, contact and other information and links to your social media channels (if you are an artist) or logos, contact and other information and links to social media channels of the artists, labels or venues you represent (if you are an agent). - Geographic location. - Login credentials for third-party websites. We also aggregate information on what Viberate.com visitors (whether logged into the Service or not) access while browsing the website. However, you are the one in control of our possibility to collect and retain your personal information. You may contact us to delete any/all of your personal information and you can completely delete your account at any time. For further information, please read the instructions in “Managing your Information” section.

#### Use of Information

We use collected information for several purposes, such as Services provision, identification and authentication, Services maintenance and improvement, new services development, Services customization (recommendation), contact, internal record keeping and research. All collected information helps us to maintain the quality of our Services and to protect you from any unauthorized action. The information we collect is not distributed, sold or leased to third parties for commercial purposes, except to provide Services you’ve requested or for other purposes when we have your permission or when we are obliged to do so. With your consent, we may also use your personal information to send you promotional information about new Services, Service updates, features, special offers or information about third parties which we think you may find interesting. Please note: If you do not give or you revoke consent to receive promotional information, you will continue to receive system emails which are necessary for the operation of the Services that we provide. You may give or revoke consent to receive promotional information at the registration process or in your profile info. We are obliged to disclose personally identifiable information to take action regarding any illegal activities, or as otherwise required by law. Viberate.com may contain links to other sites on the Internet which are owned and operated by third parties. You acknowledge that Viberate shall not be held responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this Privacy Policy.

#### Managing Your Information

We store collected information until it is no longer necessary to provide our Services, or until your account is deleted, whichever comes first. This is a case-by-case determination that depends on things like the nature of the information, why it is collected and processed, and relevant operational or legal retention needs.

  If you would like to manage, change, limit, or delete your information, we allow you to do so through the following tools:

  *  **What do we have?:** If you would like to receive  the list of your personal information that we currently keep please contact [info@viberate.com](mailto:info@viberate.com).

  *  **Changing Your Personal Details:  **You may change your profile picture, name, surname, gender, location, phone number and your preferred genres in your profile at any time.

To change your personal details:

  * 1\. Log in to your Viberate account. Click on the Profile and select My Info in the menu.
  * 2\. Click on the field with information you want to change (on desktop version you will also have to click on the edit icon at the right side of the field).
  * 3\. Change the information and save the changes with the click on “Save” or “Save all” button.

  *  **Deleting Your Viberate Account:** You may delete your Viberate account at any time (including if you want to revoke your consent to our use of your information) using our in-service “Delete Account” feature. When you delete your account, all your personal details and other information we obtained during your use of the Services (including VIB tokens in your wallet) are deleted from our servers.

To permanently delete your Viberate account and all your personal details:

  * 1\. Log in to your Viberate account. Click on the Profile and select My Info in the menu.
  * 2\. Click on the Account field (on desktop version you will also have to click on the edit icon at the right side of the field) and then on “Delete” link.
  * 3\. You will be prompted to agree with data deletion in the pop-up menu (in case you have VIB tokens in your wallet, you will also be asked to agree with your VIB tokens being lost) by checking all the boxes before continuing.

Please note: If you delete your account, all your personal details, including VIB tokens in your wallet, will be permanently deleted. This action cannot be undone.

  * 4\. For continuing the process click on “Delete my Account” button.
  * 5\. You will receive a confirmation email on the email address entered in the registration process or in account info.
  * 6\. If you are sure that you want to permanently delete your account and understand that all your VIB tokens from your wallet will be lost, click on confirmation link. After clicking, all your data will be deleted, and you will be redirected to “Delete Successful” page.

Please note: For security reasons, we cannot delete an account for you. You’ll need to be able to log in to your account to delete it. If you cannot remember your password, please click on “Forgot password?” link in the Log in/Sign up form.

  We store information until it is no longer necessary to provide our services, or until your account is deleted, whichever comes first. This is a case-by-case determination that depends on things like the nature of the information, why it is collected and processed, and relevant legal or operational retention needs.
